Kraushaar Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Photographs, circa 1900-1960, Series 4:; (box 54; 0.5 ft.)
  - S: Sauter, Rudolf H.; Schreyer, Adolph; Shean, Charles M.; Shore, Henrietta M.; Shotz; Silz, Arthur (Box 54 (hol), Folder 19)
  - T: Thaulow, Fritz; Thorburn; Troyou; Twachtman, John Henry (Box 54 (hol), Folder 20)
  - U: Ufer, Walter (Box 54 (hol), Folder 21)
  - V: Van Vleet Tompkins, Frank; Vollon, Antoine (Box 54 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Unidentified: 6 photographs of [bronze] figures (Box 54 (hol), Folder 23)
- Artwork, circa 1926, circa 1938, Series 5:; (box 53; 2 items)
  This series contains 2 items: an undated print from Marguerite and William Zorach conveying a Christmas greeting and a print by an unidentified artist. Although the dates of both items are unknown, the former was originally housed with a group of undated miscellaneous notes from 1926, and the latter was filed with miscellaneous notes from 1938.
  Artwork by James Penney and Louis Bouché is found in Series 6.7.
  - Print by Marguerite and William Zorach, circa 1926 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Print by unidentified artist, circa 1938 (Box 53, Folder 46)
- Addition to the Kraushaar Galleries Records, 1885-2006, Series 6:; (boxes 55-99, BV100; 38.4 linear feet)
  The Addition to the Kraushaar Galleries Records includes business correspondence, the bulk from 1965-1978, and Christmas cards from artists; estate records of John F. Kraushaar; artists' files; financial and business records documenting sales and purchases; consignment and loan records; photographs and negatives of works of art, including 3 albums of photographs taken by Peter A. Juley; a 1933 sketchbook by James Penney, and drawings, sketches, and 4 sketchbooks by Louis Bouché.
  The series is arranged as 8 subseries:
  6.1: Correspondence, 1877-1981, bulk 1965-1978
  6.2: Estate of John F. Kraushaar, 1931, 1945-1963
  6.3: Artists' Files, circa 1930s-2005
  6.4: Financial Records, 1885-1957
  6.5: Consignments and Loans, 1899-2006
  6.6: Photographic Materials, circa 1920s-2000s, undated
  6.7: Artwork, circa 1900s-1967, undated
  6.8: Scrapbooks, 1901-1929
  - Correspondence, 1877-1981, bulk 1965-1978, 6.1:
    The bulk of this subseries is mixed incoming and outgoing correspondence dating from 1965-1978. The earliest correspondence in this collection is also located here, and is comprised primarily of incoming letters from the late 1880s to 1920s. Generally, correspondence is between the gallery and its clients, artists, institutions, and museums, regarding consignments, loans, sales, exhibitions, and other gallery operations. Found is an 1877 letter from William Schaus to Charles Kraushaar. Also found are two folders of Christmas cards with original artwork from artists Humbert Albrizio, Gifford Reynolds Beal, Werner Drewes, Walter Feldman, Edward Hopper, Andrée Ruellan, Karl Schrag, Linda Sokolowski, and Marguerite Zorach, among others. Additional correspondents found in this subseries include artists Louis Bouché, Leonard DeLonga, Kenneth Evett, Tom Hardy, John Heliker, Robert Laurent, and James Lechay. Researchers should note additional correspondence with artists, especially those represented in the 1970s-2000s, is found in Artists' Files and Consignments and Loans.
    Artists' Christmas cards and miscellaneous correspondence is filed first, followed by correspondence arranged chronologically. Chronological correspondence is filed according to original order upon accession - grouped chronologically in spans of a year and a half (i.e. January 1965 - September 1966), then arranged alphabetically. There is occasionally some slight overlap between years, generally as a result of interfiled letters from earlier years in order to maintain context.
    - Artists' Christmas Cards, 1926-1981, (2 folders) (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1877-1967, (3 folders) (Box 55, Folder 3-5)
    - Miscellaneous, To Be Filed, 1911-1953, (2 folders) (Box 55, Folder 6-7)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 55)
      - A, General, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Albrizio, Humbert, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - American Federation of Arts, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Arnest, Bernard, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Art Dealers Association of America, 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - Ba-Bh, General, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - Bi-Bq, General, 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - Br-Bz, General, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - Bacon, Peggy, 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - Baltimore Museum of Art, circa 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - Bouché, Louis, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 19)
      - Bowdoin College Museum, 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 20)
      - Brooklyn Museum of Art, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 21)
      - Burke, Ainslie, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 22)
      - Butler Institute of American Art, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 23)
      - Ca-Cn, General, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 24)
      - Co, General, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 25)
      - Cp-Cz, General, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 26)
      - National Gallery of Canada, 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 27)
      - Colby College Museum of Art, 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 28)
      - Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 29)
      - Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 30)
      - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 31)
      - Da-De, General, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 32)
      - Df-Dz, General, 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 33)
      - DeLonga, Leonard, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - E, General, 1964-1966 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Evett, Kenneth, 1964-1966 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - F, General, 1964-1966 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Fairweather-Hardin Gallery, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Far Brook School, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Feldman, Walter, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Flint Institute of Arts, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - G, General, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Glackens, Ira, 1964-1966 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Wm. E. Goodridge, Inc., 1964-1967 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Guerin, John, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - H, General, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - Art Gallery of Hamilton, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - Hardy, Tom, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - Hartell, John, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Dalzell Hatfield Galleries, 1964-1966 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - I, General, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - J, General, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 19)
      - K, General, 1964-1966 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      - Kennedy Galleries, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - Kienbusch, William, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 22)
      - L, General, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 23)
      - Lasker, Joe, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 24)
      - Laurent, John, 1962, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 25)
      - Laurent, Robert, 1964-1966 (Box 56, Folder 26)
      - Lechay, James, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 27)
      - Lehigh University, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 28)
      - Leon, Dennis, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 29)
      - Lucas, Charles, Jr., 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 30)
      - Ma-Mh, General, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 31)
      - Mi-Mz, General, 1964-1966 (Box 56, Folder 32)
      - Mc, General, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 33)
      - Merida Gallery, Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 34)
      - Museum of Modern Art, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 35)
      - Morris, Carl, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 36)
      - Midtown Galleries, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 37)
      - Milwaukee Art Center, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 38)
      - Montreal Museum of Fine Arts, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 39)
      - Muncie, Wendell, Dr., 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 40)
      - Na-Ne, General, 1964-1966 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Nf-Nz, General, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - University of Nebraska, Sheldon Memorial Art Gallery, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - University of New Mexico, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - New York Newspapers and New Yorker, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Norfolk Museum, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - North Carolina Museum of Art, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - O, General, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Offin, Charles, 1964-circa 1966 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - Pa-Ph, General, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Pi-Q, General, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - Penney, James, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - Perutz, George, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - Philadelphia Museum of Art, Art Sales and Rental Gallery, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - Ra-Re, General, 1964-1966 (Box 57, Folder 17)
      - Rf-Rz, General, 1964-1966 (Box 57, Folder 18)
      - University of Rochester Memorial Art Gallery, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - Rockford Art Association, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 20)
      - Ruellan, Andrée, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 21)
      - Sa-Se, General, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 22)
      - Sf-Sr, General, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 23)
      - St-Sz, General, 1964-1966 (Box 57, Folder 24)
      - Saint Louis Museum, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 25)
      - Schrag, Karl, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 26)
      - Sloan, John, Mrs. and John Sloan Trust, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 27)
      - Smithsonian Institution, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 28)
      - South Bend Art Center, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 29)
      - Storm King Art Center, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 30)
      - T, General, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 31)
      - U, General, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 32)
      - V, General, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 33)
      - W, General, 1962, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 34)
      - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 35)
      - Wilmington Society of the Fine Arts, 1965-1967 (Box 57, Folder 36)
      - X-Y-Z, General, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 37)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 57)
      - A, General, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 38)
      - Akron Art Institute, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 39)
      - Albrizio, Humbert, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 40)
      - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 41)
      - American Federation of Arts, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 42)
      - Arnest, Bernard, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 43)
      - Art Dealers Association of America, 1967-1969 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Ba-Bh, General, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Bi-Bz, General, 1966-1969 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Baltimore Museum of Art, 1967-1969 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Bouché, Louis, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Burke, Ainslie, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Butler Institute of American Art, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Ca-Cn, General, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Co-Cz, General, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Carlin Galleries, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - Colby College, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - Da-De, General, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Df-Dz, General, 1967-1969 (Box 58, Folder 16)
      - DeLonga, Leonard, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      - E, General, 1967-1969 (Box 58, Folder 18)
      - F, General, 1967-1969 (Box 58, Folder 19)
      - Fairweather-Hardin Gallery, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 20)
      - Fort Wayne Art Institute, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 21)
      - G, General, 1967-1969 (Box 58, Folder 22)
      - Ganz, Julian, Jr., 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 23)
      - Wm. E. Goodridge, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 24)
      - Guerin, John, 1967-1969 (Box 58, Folder 25)
      - H, General, 1968-1969, (2 folders) (Box 58, Folder 26-27)
      - Dalzell Hatfield Galleries, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 28)
      - Hillstrom, R.L., Dr., 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 29)
      - I, General, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 30)
      - J, General, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 31)
      - K, General, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 32)
      - Kennedy Galleries, 1967-1969 (Box 58, Folder 33)
      - Kienbusch, William, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 34)
      - Koch, John, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 35)
      - L, General, 1967-1969 (Box 58, Folder 36)
      - Laros, Fred, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 37)
      - Lehigh University, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 38)
      - Leon, Dennis, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 39)
      - Ma-Mh, General, 1967-1969 (Box 58, Folder 40)
      - Mi-Mz, General, 1967-1969 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Mc, General, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Museum of Modern Art, 1952, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Na-Ne, General, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Nf-Nz, General, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - University of Nebraska, Sheldon Memorial Art Gallery, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - University of New Mexico, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - New York Newspapers and New Yorker, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - North Carolina Museum of Art, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - O, General, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Pa-Ph, General, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Pi-Q, General, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - Perutz, George, 1967-1969 (Box 59, Folder 14)
      - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - Philadelphia Museum of Art, Art Sales and Rental Gallery, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 16)
      - Ra-Re, General, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 17)
      - Rf-Rz, General, 1967-1969 (Box 59, Folder 18)
      - University of Rochester Memorial Art Gallery, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 19)
      - Ruellan, Andrée, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 20)
      - Rutgers University, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 21)
      - Sa-Se, General, 1967-1969 (Box 59, Folder 22)
      - Sf-Sr, General, 1967-1969 (Box 59, Folder 23)
      - St-Sz, General, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 24)
      - Saint Louis Museum, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 25)
      - Smith, James U., Jr., 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 26)
      - Smithsonian Institution, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 27)
      - Storm King Art Center, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 28)
      - T, General, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 29)
      - U, General, 1967-1969 (Box 59, Folder 30)
      - V, General, 1967-1969 (Box 59, Folder 31)
      - W, General, 1967-1969, (2 folders) (Box 59, Folder 32-33)
      - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1967-1969 (Box 59, Folder 34)
      - Wilmington Society of the Fine Arts, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 35)
      - X-Y-Z, General, 1967-1969 (Box 59, Folder 36)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 59)
      - A, General, 1968-1970 (Box 59, Folder 37)
      - Albrizio, Humbert, 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 38)
      - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 39)
      - Art Dealers Association of America, 1968-1970 (Box 59, Folder 40)
      - Ba-Bh, General, 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 41)
      - Bi-Bz, General, 1968-1970 (Box 59, Folder 42)
      - Bacon, Peggy, 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 43)
      - Beal, Gifford, Jr., and William Beal, 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 44)
      - Bouché, Louis, Mrs., 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 45)
      - Burke, Ainslie, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Butler Institute of American Art, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Ca-Cn, General, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Co-Cz, General, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - California Palace of the Legion of Honor, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Callahan, Kenneth, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Carlin Galleries, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Colby College, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - Da-De, General, 1968-1970 (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - Df-Dz, General, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - DeLonga, Leonard, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 14)
      - E, General, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - Evett, Kenneth, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 16)
      - F, General, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 17)
      - G, General, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 18)
      - Ganz, Julian, Jr., 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 19)
      - Glackens, Ira, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 20)
      - Wm. E. Goodridge, Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 60, Folder 21)
      - Guerin, John, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 22)
      - H, General, 1968-1970, (2 folders) (Box 60, Folder 23-24)
      - Hardy, Tom, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 25)
      - Hartell, John, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 26)
      - Dalzell Hatfield Galleries, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 27)
      - Heliker, John, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 28)
      - I, General, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 29)
      - J, General, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 30)
      - K, General, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 31)
      - Kennedy Galleries, 1969-1971 (Box 60, Folder 32)
      - Kienbusch, William, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 33)
      - Koch, John, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 34)
      - L, General, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 35)
      - La Hotan, Robert, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 36)
      - Lasker, Joe, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 37)
      - Laurent, John, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 38)
      - Laurent, Robert, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 39)
      - Lechay, James, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 40)
      - Lehigh University, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 41)
      - Leon, Dennis, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 42)
      - Ma-Mh, General, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 43)
      - Mi-Mz, General, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 44)
      - Mc, General, 1968-1970 (Box 60, Folder 45)
      - Morris, Carl, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 46)
      - Museum of Modern Art, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 47)
      - Na-Ne, General, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 48)
      - Nf-Nz, General, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 49)
      - National Gallery of Art, 1969-1971 (Box 60, Folder 50)
      - University of Nebraska, Sheldon Memorial Art Gallery, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 51)
      - New York Newspapers and New Yorker, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 52)
      - O, General, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Pa-Ph, General, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Pi-Q, General, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Penney, James, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Perutz, George, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Philadelphia Museum of Art, Art Sales and Rental Gallery, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Ra-Re, General, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Rf-Rz, General, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - University of Rochester Memorial Art Gallery, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Sa-Se, General, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Sf-Sr, General, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - St-Sz, General, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Saint Louis Museum, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Schnakenberg, Henry (Estate), 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - Schrag, Karl, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Sloan, John, Mrs., 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - Smith, James U., Jr., 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - Smithsonian Institution, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - Sneed Gallery 35, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 19)
      - J.B. Speed Art Museum, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 20)
      - Storm King Art Center, circa 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 21)
      - T, General, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 22)
      - U, General, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 23)
      - V, General, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 24)
      - W, General, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 25)
      - Wasey, Jane, circa 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 26)
      - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 27)
      - X-Y-Z, General, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 61)
      - A, General, 1971-1972 (Box 61, Folder 29)
      - Akron Art Institute, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 30)
      - Albrizio, Humbert, Mrs., 1971 (Box 61, Folder 31)
      - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1971-1972 (Box 61, Folder 32)
      - American Federation of Arts, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 33)
      - Art Dealers Association of America, 1971-1972 (Box 61, Folder 34)
      - Ba-Bh, General, 1969-1972 (Box 61, Folder 35)
      - Bi-Bz, General, 1970-1972 (Box 61, Folder 36)
      - Beal, Gifford, Jr., and William Beal, 1971-1972 (Box 61, Folder 37)
      - Bouché, Louis, Mrs., 1971 (Box 61, Folder 38)
      - Ca-Cn, General, 1970-1972 (Box 61, Folder 39)
      - Co-Cz, General, 1970-1972 (Box 61, Folder 40)
      - Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, 1971-1972 (Box 61, Folder 41)
      - Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1970-1972 (Box 61, Folder 42)
      - Da-De, General, 1971-1972 (Box 61, Folder 43)
      - Df-Dz, General, 1971-1972 (Box 61, Folder 44)
      - Delaware Art Museum, 1971-1972 (Box 61, Folder 45)
      - E, General, 1971-1972 (Box 61, Folder 46)
      - F, General, 1971-1972 (Box 61, Folder 47)
      - Frenkel and Company, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - G, General, 1967, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - H, General, 1970-1972, (2 folders) (Box 62, Folder 3-4)
      - Dalzell Hatfield Galleries, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Heckscher Museum, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Hillstrom, R.L., Dr., 1969, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Hom Gallery, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - I, General, 1970-1972 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - J, General, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - K, General, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - Kennedy Galleries, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - L, General, 1966-1967, 1970-1972 (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - Lowe Art Museum, University of Miami, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 14)
      - Ma-Mh, General, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 15)
      - Mi-Mz, General, 1969-1972 (Box 62, Folder 16)
      - Mc, General, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 17)
      - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 18)
      - Museum of Modern Art, 1970-1972 (Box 62, Folder 19)
      - Na-Ne, General, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 20)
      - Nf-Nz, General, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 21)
      - National Gallery of Art, 1970-1972 (Box 62, Folder 22)
      - University of Nebraska, Sheldon Memorial Art Gallery, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 23)
      - O, General, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 24)
      - Pa-Ph, General, 1970-1972 (Box 62, Folder 25)
      - Pi-Q, General, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 26)
      - Paullin, Ethel Parsons (Estate), 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 27)
      - Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 28)
      - Perutz, George, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 29)
      - Philadelphia Museum of Art, Art Sales and Rental Gallery, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 30)
      - Ra-Re, General, 1970-1972 (Box 62, Folder 31)
      - Rf-Rz, General, 1970-1972 (Box 62, Folder 32)
      - University of Rochester Memorial Art Gallery, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 33)
      - Sa-Se, General, 1970-1972 (Box 62, Folder 34)
      - St-Sz, General, 1970-1972 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Sloan, Mrs. John, 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Smith, James U., Jr., 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Smithsonian Institution, 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Sneed Gallery 35, 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Sotheby Parke-Bernet (and P.B. 84), 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - T, General, 1970-1972 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Tahir Gallery, 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - U, General, 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - V, General, 1968, 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - W, General, 1970-1972 (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - Witkin, James, 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 13)
      - X-Y-Z, General, 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 63)
      - A, General, 1972-1974, (2 folders) (Box 63, Folder 15-16)